Guide to the Lovelace Marionette Theatre Company Records, 1952-1984 CTC.1986.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Audio Recordings, 1967-1972; VI.
  - Bremen (Box 17, Reel 7)
  - Christopher Columbus? (Box 17, Reel 8)
  - Emperor's New Clothes - Lazarus, 1971 (Box 17, Reel 9)
  - Emperor's New Clothes, 1971 (Box 17, Reel 10)
  - Fanto - College tour (Box 17, Reel 11)
  - Hansel and Gretel music (Box 17, Reel 12)
  - Hansel and Gretel, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Reel 13-14)
  - Jack and the Beanstalk - Theatre version (Box 17, Reel 15)
  - Jack and the Beanstalk - Lazarus, 1969 (Box 17, Reel 16)
  - Love's the Best Doctor (Box 17, Reel 17)
  - Mask, Mime, and Marionette (Box 17, Reel 18)
  - Peter Pan (Box 17, Reel 19)
  - Peter Pan - Lazarus, 1969 (Box 17, Reel 20)
  - Pinoccio, 1968 (Box 17, Reel 21)
  - Pinoccio - Gimbel's, 1968 (Box 17, Reel 22)
  - Pooh (Box 17, Reel 23)
  - Pooh, 1972 (Box 17, Reel 24)
  - Pooh - School show (Box 17, Reel 25)
  - Princess and the Pea - Theatre version (Box 17, Reel 26)
  - Princess and the Pea (Box 17, Reel 27)
  - Princess and the Pea - School show (Box 17, Reel 28)
  - Punchinello's Past (Box 17, Reel 29)
  - Puppet Proposition (Box 17, Reel 30)
  - Puss in Boots (Box 17, Reel 31-32)
  - Puss in Boots, 1971 (Box 18, Reel 33)
  - Rapunzel (Box 18, Reel 34)
  - Red Ridinghood - Lazarus, 1972 (Box 18, Reel 35)
  - Reluctant Dragon (Box 18, Reel 36)
  - Rumpelstiltskin (Box 18, Reel 37)
  - Russian Dances (Box 18, Reel 38)
  - Sleeping Beauty - Theatre version (Box 18, Reel 39)
  - Three Billy Goats Gruff (Box 18, Reel 40-41)
  - Three Wishes (Box 18, Reel 42)
  - Three Wishes - Rike's, 1969 (Box 18, Reel 43)
  - T.A.P. Conference (Box 18, Reel 44)
  - Tom and Huck (Box 18, Reel 45)
  - Variety Show Music (Box 18, Reel 46)
  - The Toymaker (Box 18, Reel 47)
  - Wedding on the Eiffel Tower (Box 19, Reel 48)
  - Wizard of Oz (Box 19, Reel 49)
  - Unidentified (Box 19, Reel 50-53)
  - Interview with Margo Lovelace (Box 20, Cassette 1-8)